Okay, here showing that shoulder shrug to the wrist lock again.
Okay, this is a bit theoretical, it takes a lot of practice to do.
But if you practice it be surprised, I pulled this off on pretty decent grapplers from blue belts and what not, when grappling live, so if you're grappling live you could pull it off a lot of ways.
I mean there's other options I would do self defense but this, you know, when full punches are going I'll probably just come in and go to something else.
But this is a technique that you should put in your repertoire.
So this is a shoulder shrug to the wrist lock, take down and possibly an arm bar follow up if you get good at it.
So you're going to shoulder shrug that off, and then come over the top for the wrist lock.
Shoulder shrug it off, boom, and in this the elbow comes right to the hand.
Boom, right there, thumb on top, thumbs together, pair all your fingertips together, you're making, here's the wrist lock.
You're making motion here and you want to take the hand and separate the shoulder.
Here, and to do it fast I'm going to rotate the other foot back for power.
You can break his wrist here but I won't 'cause of my partner but I could easily just break his wrist on the throw, and then go to neon belly to finish.
And do some punches, elbows, whatever you want to do.
Soccer kicks right there, and then go in with the arm bar, okay.
So full speed, your shoulder shrug from the collar tie.
So here is full speed, shoulder shrug to the wrist lock to your arm bar, shrug it off.
A little fun technique you guys should practice, safely of course under professional supervision.
Hope you had fun with it.